JASON G. ALAS 2020 Kittredge St. #443 Berkeley, CA 94704 (415) 580-9967 jasongalas@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Highly-motivated worker with strong interpersonal and customer service skills, ecommerce pipelines, digital media, digital metadata, project management, people management, bug triage, and over five years of experience, and retail and customer service experience. A dedicated professional with strong skills in adaptability, and diversity.

### TECHNICAL QUALIFICATIONS

Skills: Google Sheets, Microsoft Office, Salesforce

### **SKILLS**

- Works well in groups as well as alone and gets along well with others
- Quick, rational thinker and quick learner of new skills
- Self-motivated worker who is fantastic with meeting deadlines and working under pressure
- Fluent Spanish speaker

## **EDUCATION**

Ex'pression College for Digital Arts, Emeryville, CA Bachelor of Applied Science, Animation and Visual Effects (2012)

## **EXPERIENCE**

Goodmojo November 2021 - Present

Executive Assistant (Current):

Responsible with assisting the CEO of GoodMojo with high priority tasks, mainly crafting Excel docs to streamline information for engineers to continue app building.

# Google October 2016 – January 2021

TV Partner Operations Manager (Jan '18 - Jan '21):

Responsible for managing Google Play TV content uploads and metadata in the Google Play Store for studios such as Sony Pictures, HBO, CBS and Lionsgate across 9 countries in Europe, Asia, and North America. Managed content uploads to the Google Play Store, delegated each studio's unique needs out to the TV team.

- Managed deliverables and workload for a team of 4 partner operations coordinators using internal project management tool, gCases and later on with Salesforce.
- Maintained an overall delivery time SLA on show metadata by an average of 80% for live storefront content by eliminating redundancies and improving processes
- Ensured discrepancies between storefront and metadata information were identified and quickly corrected for optimal customer experience.
- Found and reported numerous bugs to our tech team, and helped in resolving all of these. In certain cases, these solutions helped ensure content to be in SLA, as well as call out problems with our internal structures and workflows to help improve general workflows.

- Helped CBS & HBO achieve industry standard EMA avails by accepting initial drafts and working with them to improve upon the information given. This simplified my team's workload by streamlining the upload process, and ensured accuracy on the studios' ends as well.
- Participated in bi-weekly/monthly calls with partners to discuss goals, outstanding issues, and changes in operations and workflow to help improve overall customer satisfaction.

## TV Partner Operations Coordinator (Oct '16 - Jan '18):

Responsible for helping to build the Google Play library on an international scale for minor global studios, ensuring accurate and correct information regarding season pricing and show titles across multiple workflows and in house tools. In September, given responsibilities over Disney Studios in European countries (including Great Britain, France, and Germany) as well as HBO across 9 countries in Europe, Asia, and North America.

- Supported the POMs in minimizing SLA delivery time on show metadata by an average of 80%, especially concerning Next Day TV content with a low error rate

## Knobs/Outfit June 2015 - October 2016

Stock clerk: Responsible for inventory, restocking, and communication between sales team and stock room. Also worked the sales floor, dealing with customers face to face.

Intuit for managing stock, POS system

# **Dogpile Dogs** January 2015 – May 2015

Attendant: Supervised and cared for up to 30 dogs at a time.

# Vudu September 2013 – December 2014

Content Operations Specialist: Responsible for various tasks including closed caption synchronization, metadata entry, pricing, background artwork creation, and licensing/bundling.